Frances Bemis Papers, 1921-1974
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
Frances Bemis Papers
1921-1974
Bemis, Frances, d. 1974
MS 16
14 boxes (7 linear ft.)
Sophia Smith Collection Smith College Northampton, MA
Public relations specialist, radio producer, and fashion director. The Papers document Bemis's very active professional career, as well as the world of fashion in 1930s-50s New York City, giving a window into the celebrity and consumer culture of this time. Photographs make up a large portion, mainly of Bemis' fashion shows, special events, celebrities, and models. Correspondents include doll-maker Madame Alexander, Svetlana Allilueva (daughter of Josef Stalin), and many of the writers, artists, and radio and television personalities. Other materials include personal writings, scrapbooks, correspondence, and scripts.
Biographical Note
Frances Bemis was a public relations specialist, executive, writer, radio producer, and fashion director. She was born in Georgia on 25 June 1898, and she attended Oglethorpe University and the University of California. In the 1920s, she wrote columns for the Atlanta Constitution and Journal, and she started her public relations career by handling publicity for the Woman's Club of Atlanta. She accompanied her husband (probably Clarence Bemis) to New York City in the late 1920s, and it was there that she became a professional in the fields of public relations and advertising. (She used the name Frances Bemis professionally. She was married four times, but the names of her husbands and dates of the marriages are unknown). Hearn's, a Brooklyn Department Store that during the Depression declared itself "the bargain store of all the people," hired her as a fashion promoter and publicist in 1932. Bemis is responsible for numerous innovations in the field of department store publicity. She designed events that were guaranteed to garner press attention and bring crowds of entertainment-starved, Depression-Era New Yorkers to the free events at the store. She used celebrities and lavish shows with elaborate sets and costumes to promote new departments and features of the store, fashion collections, and holiday tie-ins. For example, in 1936-37, she staged a dog show, brought a psychologist to the store to counsel shoppers on their personal problems, hired legendary society woman Elsa Maxwell to emcee a fashion contest, and held a Thanksgiving Day circus in Central Park. In addition to writing scripts and coordinating production of these events, Bemis wrote lively releases for the press and radio. News of her events could often be found on the women's pages of New York papers, and occasionally, she made the front pages of the paper, as was the case when Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia opened ceremonies for Forgotten Man Day in 1934, a response to the National Recovery Act.
In 1938, Bemis left Hearn's department store to do free-lance public relations work with the Claire Wolff Agency. Among other projects, she directed a "College Girl's Day" for the Ford Motor Company at the 1939 New York World's Fair and staged a "Fashions Out of Test Tubes" event for the chemical industry. Her husband, (first name unknown) McLain, had joined the Army air force, and Bemis enlisted in the Women's Army Auxiliary Corps in 1943. She was stationed in Daytona Beach, where she gave radio addresses and staged entertainment for GIs and WAACs. She achieved the rank of corporal and was given an honorable discharge upon the urging of New York Times editor Ivan Veit. The Times sought a director for a war-time fashion show intended to vaunt New York City as a fashion capital while Parisian fashion houses languished under German occupation. The result, Bemis's "Fashions of the Times," was an unqualified success. Spectators filled the show to capacity, and the publicity did much to promote American fashion.
After the war, Bemis returned to Atlanta to become Director of Special Events at Rich's Department Store. She drew great press for her "Fashionata" show (1946-47), which used local socialites as models in a typically lavish production. In 1947, Bemis took a position as Director of Feature Events at New York City's Abraham and Strauss Department Store. She stayed at A and S until 1954 and continued her successful formula of spectacular events, luminous personalities, and innovative consumer services. Her personal interests in the fine arts, radio, and literature were reflected in several shows in which she showcased notable artists and performers, including Betty Smith (author of A Tree Grows in Brooklyn), the Met Opera's Rise Stevens, and radio and TV star Morey Amsterdam.
In 1956, Bemis moved to St. Augustine, Florida for a retirement of sorts. Though she no longer staged fashion extravaganzas, she used her considerable creative energy for civic and charitable activities. She worked as a publicist for the city of St. Augustine, wrote for the local papers, volunteered at an art gallery, and took an interest in advocacy for civil rights and the mentally ill. She was murdered in November, 1974.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Frances Bemis Papers consist of 7 linear ft. of material from her professional career and date from 1933 to 1974. Photographs make up the largest portion of the collection, but the Papers also include biographical information, correspondence, publicity, scripts, clippings, programs, and scrapbooks.
The Papers detail Bemis's busy career over decades during which professional women were often a marginal part of the work-world. The documentary evidence of Bemis's innovative transformation of the staid department store exhibition into a headline-grabbing cavalcade indicates the often-overlooked influence of professional women in the mid-twentieth century. The Papers also illustrate the world of fashion in 1930s-50s New York City and give a window into the celebrity and consumer culture of this time.
Organization of the Collection
This collection is organized into five series:
I. Biographical Materials
II. Correspondence
III. Writings
IV. Professional Activities
V. Subject Files
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The papers are open to research according to the regulations of the Sophia Smith Collection.
History of the Collection
The Frances Bemis Papers were donated to the Sophia Smith Collection in 1974 by Mary-Louise Wagman Boyer (Smith College class of 1951), the executor of Bemis's estate.
Search Terms
Bemis, Frances, d. 1974; Alexander, Madame; Huxtable, Ada Louise; McBride, Mary Margaret; Advertising--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Celebrities--New York (State)--New York--20th century; Department stores--United States--History--Sources; Fashion--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Fashion shows--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Popular culture--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Public relations--United States--History--20th century--Sources; Women executives--United States; Women in advertising--United States--History--20th century--Sources; New York (N.Y.)--Social life and customs--20th century--Sources
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS (1935-74, n.d.), 1 linear ft.
  This series includes clippings pertaining to Bemis's professional activities and photographs of Bemis and friends and acquaintances. There are photos of celebrities and of models with whom Bemis worked.
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE (1934-74, n.d.), .5 linear ft.
  This series consists largely of letters sent to Bemis that document her personal associations and professional activities. There are a small number of letters from Bemis to others. Bemis's correspondents include dollmaker Madame Alexander, Svetlana Allilueva (daughter of Josef Stalin), and many of the writers, artists, and radio and television personalities with whom Bemis worked.
- SERIES III. WRITINGS (1933-circa 1970s), .25 linear ft.
  This series includes materials from an unpublished memoir, "Barnum in Merchandising," and notes from a proposed project about older women living alone. Other personal notes in this series record Bemis's thoughts on the cultural changes of the 1960s and give insight into her less-documented private life.
- SERIES IV. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES (1933-71, n.d.), 4 linear ft.
  This series documents Bemis's public relations work. It starts with her career at Hearn's Department Store in Brooklyn and follows it through her employment for the city of St. Augustine. The material consists largely of photographs of Bemis-directed special events and exhibitions, but there are also clippings, publicity, scripts, correspondence, and other related material.
- SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES, .5 linear ft.
  This series consists of clippings, publicity, photographs, and ephemera collected by Bemis on friends and subjects of interest. Files include information about dollmaker Madame Alexander, radio personality (and Bemis friend and correspondent) Mary Margaret McBride, and Bethune Cookman College.
  There is also a scrapbook from the 1920s detailing Bemis's newspaper work. This scrapbook showcases Bemis's early career and consists of clippings of Bemis's writings as well as clippings of Bemis and her family and friends appearing in dramatic productions and social events. Another scrapbook from the 1950s documents her public relations work for St. Augustine.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS (1935-74, n.d.)
  - Press releases, etc., 1954-55, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings re: Bemis, 1936-1974, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings re: Mrs. W.H. Gillette (F. Bemis's mother), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs
    - Frances Bemis, 1947, 1950-51, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous notables (see folder for listings), 1935-36, 1953, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Clay Martin and "Lucifer" the rooster, 1974, [See also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE - Outgoing, 10 Feb 1974] (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified promotions and groups, circa 1940s, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Models and fashion
      - 1936-54 (Box 2, Folder 1-16)
      - n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE (1934-74, n.d.)
  - Outgoing
    - General, 1944-74, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Ada Louise Huxtable, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Incoming
    - General, 1934-74, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4-11)
    - Madame Alexander, 1952-74 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Allilueva, Svetlana (daughter of Josef Stalin), 1969-70 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Atkinson, Brooks, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Baldwin, Faith, 1951, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Blair, Frank, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Cannon, Poppy, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Chadwick, Florence, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Collins, Leroy, 1957-58 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Daniel, Clifton, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Falkenberg, Jinx, 1951, 1953, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Flexner, James Thomas, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Hurst, Fannie, 1951-54 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Huxtable, Ada Louise, 1957, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Kingman, Dong, 1958, 1967, 1971, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Koerner, Henry, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Lowell, Joan, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - McBride, Mary Margaret, 1945-60, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Merrill, Robert, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Murray, Kathryn, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Snow, Edward Rowe, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, 1942-43, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- SERIES III. WRITINGS (1933-circa 1970s)
  - General: includes introduction to lecture, fashion assignment, and notes for book, "A Living Doll," re: Madame Alexander, 1955, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - "Older Woman Alone": notes and research material, 1967-70, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - "Barnum in Merchandising": unpublished memoirs
    - Research material
      - Lists of events staged by Bemis and celebrities with whom she worked, 1933-54 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Annotated photographs from Hearns department store events (includes Eddie Cantor, Fannie Hurst, Al Smith), 1934-38 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
      - Clippings and notes re: celebrities, models, and "personalities" with whom Bemis worked, 1943, 1959, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Notes from agent and typescript (incomplete), circa 1956 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Personal notes, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 21)
- SERIES IV. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES (1933-71, n.d.)
  - Hearn's Department Store, 1933-37
    - Buy American, Feb 1933 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - NRA Ceremonies, 11 Sep 1933 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Forgotten Man Day (includes photo of Fiorello La Guardia), Nov 1935 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Dog Show with Dave Irwin, Jan 1936 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Gala Fashion Showing, 16 Mar-2 Apr 1936 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - 14th Street Bus Ceremony, Apr 1936 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Opening of Children's World, 31 Aug-5 Sep 1936 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - 109th Anniversary Event, Sep 1936 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Opening of Historic Wine Caves under Brooklyn Bridge, 7 Oct 1936 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Bureau of Human Relations, Feb 1937 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Elsa Maxwell: Queen of Fashion Contest, Mar 1937 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Scrambles of 1937, 11 Nov 1937 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hearn's Circus, Thanksgiving Day, 1934-37 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Consumers Mass Meeting (includes photos of Lillian Gish, Mary Pickford, and Ed Wynn), 21 March 1938 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - A Woman's World, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1935-37, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Freelance and WAAC career, 1937-42
    - Fashions by Television, 18 Nov 1937 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Astra Elephant Ceremonies (includes photos of Al Smith), Oct 1938 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Century Ribbon Show, Oct 1939 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Paris Review of Coney Furs, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - College Day, Oct 1939 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Fashions Out of Test Tubes, 7 Dec 1939 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - March Carnival of Advertising Women of New York, 15 Mar 1940 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Textiles of Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow, 13 Apr 1940 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Fashions of Yesterday, Today, and Tomorrow, 29-30 Aug 1941 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - The American Trend, 24 Sep 1940 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Defense Bonds for the Fur Industry, 10 Nov 1941 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Cottons for Victory, 2 Dec 1942 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Women's Army Auxiliary Corps career, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Keep 'em in Stitches, 12 Jan 1944 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - War Bond Frolics, 14 Feb 1944 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Rich's Department Store: miscellaneous, 1946, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - "Fashions of the Times," 1942-45 (Box 6, Folder 1-7)
  - "Fashionata" for Rich's, 1946-47
    - Script and production information, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, publicity, programs, and photographs, 1946-47, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2-6)
    - Script, production information, and miscellany, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 7-9)
  - Abraham and Straus, 1947-54
    - Stationery (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Contemporama, 5 Aug 1947 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Openings
      - Floor for Better Living, Sep 1947 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Junior Size Center, Oct 1947 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - Music Center (includes photos of Vic Damone and Rise Stevens), 10 Feb 1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Art to Live With, 26 Jul 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Petticoat Parade, 10 Mar 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Launching of Betty Smith's Tomorrow Will Be Better (includes photos of Smith (author of A Tree Grows in Brooklyn)), 5 Aug 1948 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Spring Tonic, 11 Mar 1949 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - White House Housekeeper, 25 Apr 1949 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Spending for Happiness, 19 May 1949 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Elizabeth Arden Beauty Classes, 13-17 Jun 1949 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Eternally Young (includes photos of Billie Burke), 20 Jun 1949 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Better Living with Television, 20 Jul 1949 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Back to School Fashion Primer (includes photos of Robin Morgan), 1 Sep 1949 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Glamour Career Fashion Show for Savings Bank Girls, 8 Sep 1949 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - What Makes a Woman Beautiful, 19-22 Sep 1949 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Ski World Opening and Ski Queen Contest, 10 Dec 1949 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Men's Short Pants, 1 Feb 1950 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Homemaker's Carnival, 13-25 Feb 1950 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Margaret O'Brien, 18 Feb 1950 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - T.H. Robijohn-Gibbings, 18 Apr 1950 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Painting for Pleasure, 8-17 Jun 1950 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - The 1950 Bride and Her Home, 24-25 Jul 1950 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Penny Contest, week of 26 Jul 1950 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Howard Hodge, 5 Sep 1950 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Book and Music Week (includes photos of Fannie Hurst, Rise Stevens, Barbara Stanwyck, and Frank Sinatra), week of 25 Sep 1950 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Maidenform Dream Fashion Show, 5 Oct 1950 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Youth after 40, 9 Oct 1950 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Christmas Promotion, Dec 1950 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Brooklyn through the Eyes of Brooklyn Artists, 22-31 Jan 1951 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Junior Fashion Show, Feb 1951 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Homemaker's Carnival, 12-24 Feb 1951 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Children's Easter Fair, 8-15 Mar 1951 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Tulip Fair, 23-28 Apr 1951 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Dog Beauty Show, 3 May 1951 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - "A Tree Grows in Brooklyn" (includes photos of Betty Smith), 8 May 1951 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Beauty and Fashion Fair, 21 May 1951 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - "Experiences Abroad," script of Bemis on Mary Margaret McBride's radio show, 5 Sep 1951 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Music, TV, and Book Week (includes photos of Morey Amsterdam, Anna May Wong, Robert Merrill, Carol Channing, and Rise Stevens), week of 24 Sep 1951 (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
    - Beauty Salon Opening, 15-20 Oct 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Christmas Doll Tea Party, 28 Nov 1951 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Good Design Exhibit, 28 Nov 1951 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Opening of A&S Nassau store, Jan-Mar 1952 (Box 10, Folder 12-13)
    - Eyes on Israel, 8 Apr 1952 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Book and Authors Tea, 13 May-17 Jun 1952 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Waiting for Baby, 5 Jun 1952 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Ladies Baseball Clinic (includes photos of Jackie Robinson), 27 Jun 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Home Fashion Time, 5 Sep 1952 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - UNESCO Delegates Event, 18 Sep 1952 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1951-52 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - British Royal Family Coronation Robes (includes photographs of Beatrice Lillie), Jan 1953 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - The Coronation Story (includes photographs of Robin Morgan), 25 May-6 Jun 1953 (Box 11, Folder 9-12)
    - Featuring Brooklyn, 27 Feb-7 Mar 1953 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Travel time, week of 5 May 1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Merrie Christmas Shop opening, 7 Nov 1953 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - The Ding Dong Lady, 14 Nov 1953 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Christmas Dress Party, 3 Dec 1953 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Authors Week, 23-27 Feb 1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Preview of Easter, 15-22 Mar 1954 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Travel Time Is Cotton Time, 17-22 May 1954 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Designs in Scandinavia, 20 Apr-16 May 1954 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1955-56
    - Fashion Is a Golden Door--Inspiration Gala, a Tribute to Michelle Murphy, 2 Mar 1955 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Jane Harris, Ltd., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Speaking engagements, 1950-56 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - City of St. Augustine, 1956-71
    - Public relations forum, 4 Oct 1956 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - "The Florida Story," Nov 1956 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Welcome to newcomers, Feb-Apr 1957 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Organization for improved St. George St., 1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Easter week, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Easter week festival, 29 Mar-5 Apr 1959 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - St. Augustine Art Association
    - Exhibit, 2 Apr 1961 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Open house events, Jan 1966 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Helen Strong exhibition, 23-27 Jan 1971 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Lecture of F. Roy Carlson, 6 April n.d (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - City of St. Augustine, 1956-71
    - Miscellaneous clippings (includes articles by Bemis) (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - St. Augustine Historical Society miscellany (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Pamphlets and brochures (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 27)
- SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES
  - Friends and associates (includes clippings, publicity, and photographs)
    - Madame Alexander (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Allilueva, Svetlana (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Bethune, Mary McLeod and Bethune Cookman College (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Boyer, Mary-Lou (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Huxtable, Ada Louise (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Kenyon, Dorothy (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Kingman, Dong (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Koerner, Henry (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - McBride, Mary Margaret (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - McNaughton, Elinor (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Nemkov, Sol (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Weddell, Mimi (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous friends' obituaries (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - General
    - Art
      - Midtown Gallery (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Museum and Brooklyn Children's Museum (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Civil rights (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Echo House, St. Augustine (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - The Lightner Museum, St. Augustine (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous material collected by Frances Bemis (includes annotated clippings and memorabilia) (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Clippings from the Atlanta Journal, 1921-32 (Box 14)
    - Public Relations Program for the City of St. Augustine, 1956-57 (Box 14)
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS
  - SERIES IV. PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITES
    - Posters (Map-case Flat File)